/*
   Monday, July 5, 20213:03:14 PM
   User: 
   Server: .\SQLEXPRESS
   Database: 
   Application: 
*/

'StockUp' table
- Unable to create index 'PK_StockUp'.  
The CREATE UNIQUE INDEX statement terminated because a duplicate key was found for the object name 'dbo.StockUp' and the index name 'PK_StockUp'. The duplicate key value is (0).
Could not create constraint. See previous errors.
The statement has been terminated.

